Listen, sir, for the last time,
I don't care what the computer says.
We did not take a bag of Mashuga Nuts
from the minibar.
And we did not watch
Dr. Do-Me-A-Little.
-Joey, were you in our room last night?
-No.
I was told the name of the movie
would not appear on the bill.
-We're checking out of the bridal suite.
-That's right, I'm no longer a bride.
I'll never be a bride again.
Now I'm just someone's wife.
And I'm the happiest guy in the world.
Honey, don't be upset. We still have
so much to look forward to.
Yeah, right.
-We got the honeymoon.
-That's not till Thursday.
-The wedding pictures.
-It won't be ready for weeks.
Not the disposable cameras
from the tables.
That's true.
I knew I married you for a reason!
Tell you what, I will go get them
developed, and you can go home.
-What? What did you take a picture of?
-Nothing.
It was something.
Ross has the cameras.
Has he checked out yet?
Are you joking?
Checkout is not till noon.
-And he has a good 11 minutes left.
-So?
So Ross had never checked out of a room
a minute before he had to.
One time, when we were dating,
we got a late checkout.
He got so excited,
it was the best sex we ever had.
Until he screamed out "Radisson"
at the end.
Okay, well, I'm gonna get Ross,
get the cameras and get them developed.
32, Joe. You're 32!
-Here's a copy of your bill.
-Thanks.
Champagne, strawberries..
Oh, my God! I can't believe Chandler
ordered porn on our wedding night.
Yeah, that's sad.
Mashuga Nut?
I have six minutes left!
It's me.
Soaps, shampoos.
Are you really taking all this stuff?
Why not?
It's built into the price of the room.
Yeah, but you don't need..
What is this?
Thread.
Score!
-Where are the disposable cameras?
-What cameras?
-Last night I asked you to take them.
-No, you didn't.
Yes, remember?
Right before we cut the cake, I said..
Yeah, you asked me
if I could do you a favor.
Then my Uncle Murray came up to you
and handed you a check.
Then you said, "Why is it called a check?
Why not a Yugoslavian?"
Then you did that,
and my Uncle Murray looked at me like:
-So you don't have the cameras?
-No, sorry.
So, what? They're gone?
Monica's gonna freak!
I'm sure they're here somewhere.
I'll help you look.
-Great.
-In three minutes.
Are you gonna open the presents
without Chandler?
No! I'm just..
They're calling out to me.
This little guy even crawled up in my lap.
Chandler wouldn't mind if I opened just
one present. What do you think it is?
A little mirror that,
when you look into it..
you see yourself as an old woman.
A tiny salt shaker!
Oh, my God, for tiny salt!
Oh, wow! Okay. Well, that was fun.
That was fun.
Okay, I'll just wait for Chandler
to open up the rest of them.
Although, you know, this is part
of a salt-and-pepper set.
It may just count as only half a present.
What do you think?
I guess it's okay to open one more if it's
part of a set. It's probably this one.
Or this one!
-How are you? Got any morning sickness?
-The guys don't know yet, do they?
Joey and Ross don't know anything.
Chandler thinks Phoebe's pregnant.
That's right.
Chandler does still think I'm pregnant.
He hasn't asked me how I'm feeling
or offered to carry my bags.
I feel bad for the woman
who ends up with him.
After you, of course.
Don't worry. You only have to be
pregnant for a few more hours..
because I'm telling the father today.
Is it someone in the building?
That tall guy on the first floor?
-No!
-What? I think he's cute.
-Then you have his baby.
-Believe me, I'm trying.
It's so weird.
You're gonna tell this guy today..
and he has no idea
what's gonna happen.
You're just gonna knock on his door
and change his life forever.
You're like Ed McMahon,
except without the big check.
Or the raw sexual magnetism.
Yeah, well, I guess
it is pretty big news.
Pretty big? It's huge!
God, this guy doesn't have a clue.
He's just walking down the street thinking,
"I had sex with Rachel Greene. I rock!"
Then, bam! He's a father,
everything's different.
It's only different if he wants it to be.
I'm not gonna ask him for anything.
He still has this huge decision
to make.
Now he's walking around thinking,
"Do I want to be a dad?" Then, bam!
What was that "bam"?
I don't know.
He's hit by a bus, or something.
Joey, what would you do if someone you
slept with told you she was pregnant?
Who called here?
Did she sound blond? Did she have
an accent? I gotta make a call.
Should have never walked
into that Sunglass Hut!
It's not you!
You didn't get anybody pregnant.
Why would you scare me like that?
What the hell's going on?
Is somebody pregnant?
Oh, yeah! That's me.
Oh, my God, Pheebs!
You're gonna have a baby?
Yes, I am.
Oh, my God, I'm gonna have a baby!
-Wait a minute, who's the father?
-You don't know him.
It's not important. He wants nothing
to do with me or the baby.
Who is this guy? Because I will
track him down and kick his ass!
-David Linn.
-David Linn!
-Who's David Linn?
-Some guy from my gym. Little annoying.
-Chandler?
-Did you find the cameras?
-No. Did you?
-Yes.
That's why I'm under the table,
celebrating.
I checked in the lost and found. I talked
to the manager. No one's turned them in.
Great. Those cameras were the only thing
that was gonna cheer Monica up today.
You just got married.
Why is she so depressed?
All my energy is going
into not asking that question.
-I can't believe I screwed this up!
-I'm sorry, man.
Here's a thought.
This is the same ballroom.
There's a band. There's gonna be
plenty of dressed-up people.
Are you suggesting
we dance our troubles away?
No, I'm saying we buy more of these
at the gift shop..
throw our tuxes back on
and take a few pictures.
We just have to make sure
not to get anybody's faces.
Are you serious?
I'm thinking about
your new bride at home.
Do you want to start your life together
by letting her down?
Marriage advice? Really?
I'm telling you,
this looks exactly like your wedding.
-Aren't these the same flowers?
-I don't know. Monica picked them.
-What about the chairs?
-Those too.
-The place settings?
-Her.
-What did you do?
-I was in charge of the cameras.
Gift shop?
-Did you do it yet?
-Not yet.
Then what are you doing here?
Are you about to do it?
Is it Gunther?
-It's not Gunther!
-Thank God. Because that hair on a baby?
The father is not here, okay?
I haven't told him yet.
-I don't think I can tell him at all now.
-Why not?
I was walking down the street, thinking,
"I'm gonna tell the father." And then, bam!
Bus?
No, you! You freaked me out.
You kept saying how huge this all is.
But it is huge.
I know. But I was just thinking about
how huge it was for me.
I didn't even go to how huge it'll be
for the father.
You're thinking about this way too much.
Just tell him and get it over with.
It's like ripping off this Band-Aid,
quick and painless. Watch.
Oh, mother of..!
See?
-Are we opening presents?
-No. I shouldn't have even opened these.
Joey, I am out of control!
You have to do me a favor.
No matter what I say,
no matter what I do..
please, do not let me open
another present. Okay?
Give me one more.
Oh, good, you're here.
Pheebs? Listen..
-Sit down, I got something I wanna say.
-All right.
It's a scary world out there,
especially for a single mom.
I've always felt that you
and I have a special bond.
So..
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
Oh, my God!
Oh, yeah, I'll marry you.
-You can't marry him!
-Hey, lady, your day's over. It's my turn.
-Why can't she marry me?
-I can and I will.
She's not pregnant.
Rachel's the one who's pregnant.
Oh, my God!
He'd notice when you didn't
have a baby in nine months!
It's Joey!
I love you.
Wait, I can't believe it!
Rachel's pregnant? Who's the father?
We don't know.
-I wonder if it's that dude.
-There's a dude?
Who is it?
About a month ago
this guy spent the night with Rachel.
I didn't see who it was, but..
Was that story over?
The guy left this.
Oh, my God!
I know who the father is.
People have got
to finish their stories.
Hello.
I don't know if we're both in.
Come closer.
Nice aftershave.
If you want some,
I've got eight mini bottles in my bag.
-Excuse me, could you take a picture of us?
-Of course.
Would you take one of us?
Yeah, sure.
Click.
-It didn't click.
-I heard it.
-But there was no flash.
-Why won't you take our picture?
Oh, yeah. I'll take your picture.
Your finger was covering the lens.
Who are you, Ansel Adams?
Get out of here!
Look, I feel really bad about
how I freaked you out before..
so I asked the father to meet you here
so you could tell him.
What? Wait a minute.
How do you even know who the father is?
I may play the fool at times..
but I'm more than a pretty blond girl
with an ass that won't quit.
I believe this belongs
to the father of your baby..
Oh, God. He's in there right now?
You can turn around, or you can go rip
the Band-Aid off. What do you want to do?
-Let's rip.
-Are you sure?
-Phoebe!
-Okay. Sorry.
Hey, Rach.
Why don't you go up on-stage.
I'll get a picture of you doing the speech.
Will the owner of a 1995 Buick LeSabre
please see the front desk?
Your car is about to be towed.
That's my car!
-A '95 LeSabre?
-Yes.
-A green LeSabre?
-Yes!
-I'm sorry, I meant a blue LeSabre.
-Yes, green-blue.
Well, go. Go move it!
Ready for the last picture?
Get ready to run.
Congratulations on your wedding.
So, what's this about?
Rachel has something
she wants to tell you.
And I believe that
this is your red sweater.
No, this is my red sweater.
Oh, no.
Could I get anyone a coffee?
Or poison? No? Just for me? Okay.
What's going on, Rach?
Nothing.
Phoebe kind of made a mistake.
But you do wear that sweater a lot.
Are you involved in some kind of dare?
I'm actually glad Phoebe called.
I know we broke up because you thought
I was immature, but I've grown up.
I think we should get back together.
It's just not the right time.
It is the right time.
I'm ready for more.
Come on, Rach.
Let's give it another try.
I'm having a baby.
-You can go.
-Thank you.
I don't know how
any of these got opened!
-You opened them all?
-I know, I am a terrible person.
Chandler's never gonna trust me
with anything ever again.
You got my parents' gift.
-What is that?
-I think it does something to salami.
-How'd it go?
-What did Tag say?
Tag is not the father.
And Joey knows now?
I do, Rach, I do.
And I am so happy for you.
Wow, you didn't even try
to unhook my bra.
-So are you ever gonna tell whoever it is?
-I will. I'm just not up for it tonight.
No matter what this guy says,
you're not gonna be alone in this.
-I'm not?
-No. Listen..
It's a scary world out there,
especially for a single mom.
I've always felt like you and I have
this special bond, you know?
-Rachel Greene, will you marry me?
-What?
-What?!
-Pheebs, give me the ring back.
-No!
Joey, you're so sweet, so sweet, honey.
But I'm not looking for a husband.
I understand.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go and lie down.
What? I proposed to you.
It balances out.
I can't say that didn't hurt.
But I'll take you back, Joey Tribbiani.
-Listen, about that, I only offered..
-Ooh, a Salami Buddy!
There you go!
-We're back!
-Great.
We're hanging in the kitchen.
Let's stay in the kitchen.
-It's picture time.
-You're gonna love these.
Here's a picture of Ross.
And that's me.
And that's me and Ross.
And here's a picture of our first kiss
as a married couple.
Wow, that is a great picture. Yeah!
And interesting, because I found
the cameras in one of our bags.
Didn't see that coming.
So this isn't a picture
of our first kiss..
but it is a picture
of my first kiss with this lady.
Which, by the look on your face, I'm sure
you'll remember, so there's no need..
-I'll take the real pictures to get developed.
-Good idea.
You opened all the presents without me?
We were gonna do that together.
You kissed another woman?!
-Call it even?
-Okay.
-I'm gonna go get these in some water.
-You stole those from that wedding?
No, the hotel lobby. They think they can
charge me for some dirty movie..
and a bag of Mashuga Nuts,
they got another thing coming!
Hey, my sweater!
I've been looking for this
for, like, a month.
Oh, my God!
-Hey, how you doing?
-Good. Long time no see.
-Like your sweater.
-Right back at you.
-It's crazy about Rachel.
-Well, she's one crazy lady.
-So whose is it?
-I don't know, some Italian guy.
Come on, read your own label.
See you later. He is so weird.